Guide to the Records of the Office of the Chancellor and Executive Vice President: David D. Henry and Carroll V. Newsom, John E. Ivey, Jr., George D. Stoddard, and Russell D. Niles 1942-1966 (Bulk 1952-1956) RG 6.0
New York University Archives
- Series III: George D. Stoddard, 1960-1964
  - Subseries B: 1960 - 1961
    - Space - Washington Square Southeast Project, 1960-1961 (Box 60, Folder 12)
    - Special Projects - Aging Study, 1960-1961 (Box 61, Folder 1)
      bar code: 3 1142 042255359
    - Special Projects - Albany Program, 1960-1961 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - Special Projects - Bell Telephone/Engineering Program, 1960-1961 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Special Projects - Ellis Island, 1960-1961 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - Special Projects - French and American Sciences, Symposium, 1960-1961 (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - Special Projects - Loeb Student Center, 1960-1961 (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Special Projects - Puerto Rico Project, 1960-1961 (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - Special Projects - Television Instruction, 1960-1961 (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Subseries C: 1961 - 1962
    - Administration - Business Office, 1961-1962 (Box 61, Folder 9)
    - Administration - President, Office of, 1961-1962 (Box 61, Folder 10)
    - Administration - Research Services, Office of, 1961-1962 (Box 61, Folder 11)
    - Administration - Secretary, Office of, 1961-1962 (Box 61, Folder 12)
    - Administration - Trustees, Board of, 1961-1962 (Box 61, Folder 13)
    - Admissions, 1961-1962 (Box 61, Folder 14)
    - Admissions and Registration, 1961-1962 (Box 61, Folder 15)
    - Admissions - Registrar, 1961-1962 (Box 61, Folder 16)
    - Associations - American Council of Education, 1961-1962 (Box 61, Folder 17)
    - Committees - Appointments, 1961-1962 (Box 62, Folder 1)
      bar code: 3 1142 042255367
    - Committees - Scholarship Regulation, 1961-1962 (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - Committees - School of Arts and Science, 1961-1962 (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - Faculty Appointments, 1961-1962 (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - Faculty Prospects, 1961-1962 (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - Fundraising, 1961-1962 (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - General Education, 1961-1962 (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - Government - New York State (Education) Department, 1961-1962 (Box 62, Folder 8)
    - Government - U.S. Air Force, 1961-1962 (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - Government - U.S. Army, 1961-1962 (Box 62, Folder 10)
    - International - Iranian Project, 1961-1962 (Box 62, Folder 11)
    - International - Universities (Japan, Nigeria, Ghana), 1961-1962 (Box 62, Folder 12)
    - Libraries, 1961-1962 (Box 63, Folder 1)
      bar code: 3 1142 042255375
    - Schools - Athletics, 1961-1962 (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - Schools - College of Arts and Science, 1961-1962 (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - Schools - Communications Arts Group, 1961-1962 (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - Schools - Courant Institute of Mathematical Sciences, 1961-1962 (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - Schools - Courant Institute of Mathematical Sciences, 1961-1962 (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - Schools - Dentistry, 1961-1962 (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - Schools - Education, 1961-1962 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Schools - Education (School for Children), 1961-1962 (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - Schools - Engineering, 1961-1962 (Box 63, Folder 10)
    - Schools - General Education, 1961-1962 (Box 63, Folder 11)
    - Schools - Graduate School of Arts and Science, 1961-1962 (Box 63, Folder 12)
    - Schools - Graduate School of Business Administration, 1961-1962 (Box 63, Folder 13)
    - Schools - Graduate School of Public Administration, 1961-1962 (Box 64, Folder 1)
      bar code: 3 1142 042255383
    - Schools - Graduate School of Social Work, 1961-1962 (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - Schools - Institute of Fine Arts, 1961-1962 (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - Schools - Institute of Hebrew Studies, 1961-1962 (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - Schools - La Maison Francaise, 1961-1962 (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - Schools - Law, 1961-1962 (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - Schools - Medical, 1961-1962 (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - Schools - Retailing, 1961-1962 (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - Schools - Town Hall, 1961-1962 (Box 64, Folder 9)
    - Schools - University College, 1961-1962 (Box 64, Folder 10)
    - Schools - Washington Square College, 1961-1962 (Box 64, Folder 11)
    - Space - Planning Group (School for Children), 1961-1962 (Box 64, Folder 12)
    - Space - Warren Weaver Hall (Courant Institute), 1961-1962 (Box 64, Folder 13)
    - Special Projects, 1961-1962 (Box 64, Folder 14)
    - Special Projects - Graduate Institute of Book Publishing, 1961-1962 (Box 64, Folder 15)
    - Graduate Institute of Book Publishing, 1961-1962 (Box 64, Folder 16)
    - Special Projects - Hall of Fame, 1961-1962 (Box 65, Folder 1)
      bar code: 3 1142 042255391
    - Special Projects - Puerto Rico Culture Center, 1961-1962 (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Students - Dean of Students, 1961-1962 (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Students - Foreign Student Center, 1961-1962 (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Students - Glee Club, 1961-1962 (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - Students - Loeb Student Center, 1961-1962 (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - Students - Rhodes Scholarship, 1961-1962 (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Television - NYU Television Production Center, 1961-1962 (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - Television - College for Independent Study, 1961-1962 (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - University Health Services, 1961-1962 (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - University Health Services, 1961-1962 (Box 65, Folder 11)
    - Worlds Fair, 1961-1962 (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - Subseries D: 1962 - 1963
    - Administration - Assistant Executive Vice-President, 1962-1963 (Box 66, Folder 1)
      bar code: 3 1142 042255409
    - Administration - Assistant Executive Vice-President, 1962-1963 (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - Administration - Board of Trustees, 1962-1963 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - Administration - Controller, 1962-1963 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Administration - Radhakrishnan Visit, 1962-1963 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Administration - Coordinator of Research Services, 1962-1963 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Administration - Vice-President for University Development, 1962-1963 (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - Administration - Vice-President, 1962-1963 (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - Administration - Vice-President and Secretary, 1962-1963 (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - Administration - Vice-President for University Relations, 1962-1963 (Box 66, Folder 10)
    - Admissions, 1962-1963 (Box 67, Folder 1)
      bar code: 3 1142 042255417
    - Admissions - Scholarships, 1962-1963 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Admissions - Financial Aid, 1962-1963 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Committees - Conference on Education in the Sciences, 1962-1963 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Committees - Faculty Morale, 1962-1963 (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Committees - Graduate Work, 1962-1963 (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - Committees - Policy on Conferences, 1962-1963 (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - Committees - Records Retention, 1962-1963 (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - Faculty Appointments, 1962-1963 (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - Faculty Prospects, 1962-1963 (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - Government - Fort Bragg Visit, 1962-1963 (Box 67, Folder 11)
    - Government - New York State Education Department, 1962-1963 (Box 67, Folder 12)
    - Government - U.S. Office of Education, 1962-1963 (Box 67, Folder 13)
    - Hall of Fame, 1962-1963 (Box 67, Folder 14)
    - Housing Discrimination, 1962-1963 (Box 67, Folder 15)
    - Library, 1962-1963 (Box 67, Folder 16)
    - Library - Fales Collection, 1962-1963 (Box 67, Folder 17)
    - Library - Tamiment, 1962-1963 (Box 67, Folder 18)
    - Middle States Evaluation Committee, 1962-1963 (Box 68, Folder 1)
      bar code: 3 1142 042255425
    - Personnel, 1962-1963 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Schools - Athletics, 1962-1963 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Schools - Commerce, 1962-1963 (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - Schools - Communications Arts Group, 1962-1963 (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Schools - Courant Institute, 1962-1963 (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - Schools - Courant Institute, 1962-1963 (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - Schools - Dentistry, 1962-1963 (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - Schools - Education, 1962-1963 (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - Schools - Engineering, 1962-1963 (Box 68, Folder 10)
    - Schools - General Education, 1962-1963 (Box 68, Folder 11)
    - Schools - Graduate School of Arts and Science, 1962-1963 (Box 68, Folder 12)
    - Schools - Graduate School of Business Administration, 1962-1963 (Box 68, Folder 13)
    - Schools - Graduate School of Public Administration, 1962-1963 (Box 68, Folder 14)
    - Schools - Graduate School of Social Work, 1962-1963 (Box 68, Folder 15)
    - Schools - Institute of Fine Arts, 1962-1963 (Box 68, Folder 16)
    - Schools - Institute of Hebrew Studies, 1962-1963 (Box 68, Folder 17)
    - Schools - International Affairs, 1962-1963 (Box 68, Folder 18)
    - Schools - Law, 1962-1963 (Box 68, Folder 19)
    - Schools - Medical, 1962-1963 (Box 68, Folder 20)
    - Schools - Retailing, 1962-1963 (Box 68, Folder 21)
    - Schools - University College of Arts and Science, 1962-1963 (Box 69, Folder 1)
      bar code: 3 1142 042255433
    - Washington Square College of Arts and Science, 1962-1963 (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - Space - Catholic Student Center, 1962-1963 (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - Space - Education, School of, 1962-1963 (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - Space - Heights Plan, 1962-1963 (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - Space - Library, 1962-1963 (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - Space - University Valley, 1962-1963 (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - Space - University Valley, 1962-1963 (Box 69, Folder 8)
    - Space - Warren Weaver Hall, 1962-1963 (Box 69, Folder 9)
    - Space - Washington Square, 1962-1963 (Box 69, Folder 10)
    - Special Projects - Peace Corps, 1962-1963 (Box 69, Folder 11)
    - Special Projects - Peace Corps, 1962-1963 (Box 69, Folder 12)
    - Students, 1962-1963 (Box 70, Folder 1)
      bar code: 3 1142 042255441
    - Students - Dean John W. Knedler, Jr., 1962-1963 (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - Students - International Student Center, 1962-1963 (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - Students - Medical Health Center Services, 1962-1963 (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - University Medals, 1962-1963 (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - University Press, 1962-1963 (Box 70, Folder 6)
- Series IV: Russell D. Niles
  The administrative records of Russell D. Niles measure 11 linear feet and span the years 1964-1966. The material has been processed into three chronological series representing each of the academic years of Niles' term, and a fourth series consists of administrative topics, Deans' Council minutes and mission statements originally set apart from the chronological series. The first series contains a small number of records from the final months of the George Stoddard administration. The third series, covering the academic year 1965-1966, was insufficiently processed by a student in the fall of 1987 and the finding aid to that series is not, in its present state, reliable. The excessive bulk in the Niles collection can be attributed, to a large extent, to the processing problems in series III. It must also be noted that the subseries on all-university departments in series II contains material spanning Niles' first two academic years, 1963-1964 and 1964-1965. Some files covering student grievances, the transfer of faculty members from one school to another, and specific faculty student relations are restricted.
  In relation to the previous subgroups, Niles' records contain a substantial number of files composed of material on spaces and buildings (most notably in series III, subseries IV), reflecting the many proposed and actual physical changes taking place at NYU at this time. A file on the President of the University refers to NYU's attempt to acquire the Worlds Fair Spanish Pavilion and the Astor estate in Rhinebeck, New York. There are signs indicating the pending shutdown of the University Heights Campus and the subsequent need to strengthen Washington Square.
  The files record changes that resulted from the Self-Study Final Report and the Ford Foundation study, such as the upgrading of admissions and efforts to achieve increased centralization. Mission statements (series IV, subseries III) demonstrate how well the schools and divisions meet the recommendations of the Self Study in planning their futures. Of particular interest are a series of files on "Project Apex," a program designed to train high-school students to teach in poverty stricken areas. In addition, the first series contains a report on early experiments with LSD.
  Niles was committed to building a strong central core around the arts and sciences at NYU, making undergraduate schools his priority. The files attest to his goals and movement toward centralization that the Office of Chancellor and Executive Vice President was largely responsible for promoting. Niles administrative records show him to be in touch with all aspects of University operations and demonstrates the growth of the position since the first years of David Henrys term.
  - Subseries A: 1963 - 1964 (Includes Records of George Stoddard)
    - Sub-Subseries A: Administrative Officers
      - President, 1963 (Box 26, Folder 1)
        bar code: 3 1142 042255003
      - President, 1964 (Box 26, Folder 2)
      - Officers Group, 1963-1964 (Box 26, Folder 3)
      - Auxiliary Enterprises, 1963-1964 (Box 26, Folder 4)
      - Vice-President for University Development, 1963-1964 (Box 26, Folder 5)
      - Vice-President and Secretary, 1963-1964 (Box 26, Folder 6)
      - Vice-President, 1963-1964 (Box 26, Folder 7)
      - Vice-President for Business Management, 1964 (Box 26, Folder 8)
      - Vice-President for Business Management, 1963-1964 (Box 26, Folder 9)
      - Vice-President for University Relations, 1962-1963 (Box 26, Folder 10)
      - Institutional Research, 1963-1964 (Box 26, Folder 11)
      - Assistant Executive Vice-President, 1964 (Box 26, Folder 12)
      - Treasurer and Controller, 1963-1964 (Box 26, Folder 13)
      - Coordinator of Research Services, 1960-1963 (Box 26, Folder 14)
      - Coordinator of Research Services, 1964 (Box 26, Folder 15)
      - Coordinator of Research Services, 1964 (Box 26, Folder 16)
      - Administrative Council, 1963-1964 (Box 26, Folder 17)
      - Dean of Admissions, 1961-1963 (Box 26, Folder 18)
      - Dean of Admissions, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 1)
        bar code: 3 1142 042255011
      - Dean of Financial Aid, 1962-1963 (Box 27, Folder 2)
      - Dean of Financial Aid, 1963-1964 (Box 27, Folder 3)
      - Dean of Financial Aid, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 4)
      - Registrar, 1963-1964 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Sub-Subseries B: Administrative Subject Files
      - Alumni, General, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 6)
      - Committee to Coordinate Planning and Space Related Projects and Research, 1963-1964 (Box 27, Folder 7)
      - Committee on Coordinated Liberal Studies, 1962-1963 (Box 27, Folder 8)
      - Committee on Coordinated Liberal Studies, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 9)
      - Committee on Coordinated Liberal Studies, 1963-1964 (Box 27, Folder 10)
      - Committee on Coordinated Liberal Studies, 1964-1966 (Box 27, Folder 11)
      - Committee for Main Block Utilization, 1963-1964 (Box 27, Folder 12)
      - Deans Council, 1961-1964 (Box 27, Folder 13)
      - General File, A-Z, 1961-1963 (Box 27, Folder 14)
      - General File, A-Z, 1963-1964 (Box 27, Folder 15)
      - Government - National Science Foundation, 1962-1964 (Box 28, Folder 1)
        bar code: 3 1142 042255029
      - Government - National Science Foundation, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 2)
      - Government - New York Department of Education, 1962-1964 (Box 28, Folder 3)
      - Librarian, 1963-1964 (Box 28, Folder 4)
      - Miscellaneous Consultants, 1963 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Sub-Subseries C: Schools, Divisions, and Institutions
      - Executive Dean of Arts and Science, 1962-1964 (Box 28, Folder 6)
      - Executive Dean of Business Schools, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 7)
      - Athletics, Division of, 1963-1964 (Box 28, Folder 8)
      - College of Engineering, 1962-1963 (Box 28, Folder 9)
      - College of Engineering, 1963-1964 (Box 28, Folder 10)
      - College of Engineering, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 11)
      - Commerce, School of, 1962-1964 (Box 28, Folder 12)
      - Communications Arts Group, 1963-1964 (Box 28, Folder 13)
      - Courant Institute of Mathematics, 1961-1963 (Box 29, Folder 1)
        bar code: 3 1142 042255037
      - Courant Institute of Mathematics, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 2)
      - Courant Institute - Warren Weaver Hall Construction, 1961-1964 (Box 29, Folder 3)
      - Dentistry, School of, 1963-1964 (Box 29, Folder 4)
      - Education, School of, 1963-1964 (Box 29, Folder 5)
      - Fine Arts, Institute of, 1963-1964 (Box 29, Folder 6)
      - General Education, Division of, 1963-1964 (Box 29, Folder 7)
      - Graduate School of Business Administration, 1962-1964 (Box 29, Folder 8)
      - Graduate School of Arts and Science, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 9)
      - Graduate School of Arts and Science - Committee for the Selection of New Dean, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 10)
      - Graduate School of Public Administration, 1963-1964 (Box 29, Folder 11)
      - Graduate School of Social Work, 1963-1964 (Box 29, Folder 12)
      - Hall of Fame, 1963-1964 (Box 29, Folder 13)
      - Hebrew Studies, Institute of, 1963 (Box 29, Folder 14)
      - Law, School of, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 15)
      - Medicine, School of, 1960-1964 (Box 29, Folder 16)
      - Project Apex, 1964 (Box 30, Folder 1)
        bar code: 3 1142 042255045
      - Research, 1963-1965 (Box 30, Folder 2)
      - Retailing, School of, 1964 (Box 30, Folder 3)
      - Retailing, Graduate School of, 1963-1964 (Box 30, Folder 4)
      - Town Hall, 1963-1964 (Box 30, Folder 5)
      - University College of Arts and Science, 1963-1964 (Box 30, Folder 6)
      - Washington Square College of Arts and Science, 1963-1964 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Sub-Subseries E: Space
      - Space - Miscellaneous, 1961-1963 (Box 30, Folder 8)
        - Letter from Martin L. Beck to Marcel Breuer, 1963 (Box 30)
      - Space - Miscellaneous, 1963 (Box 30, Folder 9)
      - Space - Miscellaneous, 1963-1964 (Box 30, Folder 10)
      - Space - University Heights, 1964 (Box 30, Folder 11)
        - Letter from Martin L. Beck to Hamilton Smith, 1964 (Box 30)
      - Space - Washington Square, 1963-1964 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Sub-Subseries F: Students
      - Dean of Students, 1962-1964 (Box 30, Folder 13)
      - Dean of Students, 1964 (Box 30, Folder 14)
      - Foreign Student Program, 1964 (Box 31, Folder 1)
        bar code: 3 1142 042255052
      - Students - General, 1963-1964 (Box 31, Folder 2)
      - Glee Club, 1963-1964 (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - Housing, 1955-1962 (Box 31, Folder 4)
      - Housing, 1962 (Box 31, Folder 5)
      - Loeb Student Center, 1964 (Box 31, Folder 6)
      - Religious Center, 1964 (Box 31, Folder 7)
      - Student Housing Facilities, 1963 (Box 31, Folder 8)
      - Tuition Increases, 1960-1963 (Box 31, Folder 9)
      - Joe Weinstein Halls, 1963-1964 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Subseries B: 1964 - 1965
    - Sub-Subseries A: Administrative Officers
      - President, 1964-1965 (Box 31, Folder 11)
      - Vice-President, 1964-1965 (Box 31, Folder 12)
      - Vice-President for University Development, 1964 (Box 31, Folder 13)
      - Vice-President for University Development, 1965 (Box 31, Folder 14)
      - Vice-President for Business, 1964-1965 (Box 31, Folder 15)
      - Assistant Vice-President for Business Management, 1965 (Box 31, Folder 16)
      - Vice-President and Secretary, 1964-1965 (Box 31, Folder 17)
      - Vice-President for University, 1964-1965 (Box 32, Folder 1)
        bar code: 3 1142 042255060
      - Treasurer and Controller, 1964-1965 (Box 32, Folder 2)
      - Assistant Executive Vice-President, 1964-1965 (Box 32, Folder 3)
      - Budget Advisory Group, 1964 (Box 32, Folder 4)
      - Budget Advisory Group, 1964-1965 (Box 32, Folder 5)
      - Budget Advisory Group, 1965 (Box 32, Folder 6)
      - Budget Advisory Group, 1965 (Box 32, Folder 7)
      - Board of Trustees, 1963-1965 (Box 32, Folder 8)
      - Board of Trustees - Appointments, 1963-1964 (Box 32, Folder 9)
      - Board of Trustees - Appointments, 1964-1965 (Box 32, Folder 10)
      - Budget Coordinator, 1963-1965 (Box 32, Folder 11)
      - Business Manager, 1964-1965 (Box 32, Folder 12)
      - Officers Group - Minutes, 1964-1965 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Sub-Subseries B: Administration Subject Files
      - Admissions, 1964 (Box 32, Folder 14)
      - Admissions, 1964-1965 (Box 32, Folder 15)
      - Alumni Federation, 1965 (Box 32, Folder 16)
      - American Council on Education, 1963-1964 (Box 32, Folder 17)
      - Applicants, 1964-1965 (Box 32, Folder 18)
      - Applicants, 1964-1965 (Box 33, Folder 1)
        bar code: 3 1142 042255078
      - Art Collection, University, 1962 (Box 33, Folder 2)
      - Athletics, Committee on, 1965 (Box 33, Folder 3)
      - Athletics, Division of, 1964 (Box 33, Folder 4)
      - Attorney, University, 1965 (Box 33, Folder 5)
      - Communication Arts Group, 1964 (Box 33, Folder 6)
      - Deans Council, 1964-1965 (Box 33, Folder 7)
      - Financial Aid, 1963-1964 (Box 33, Folder 8)
      - Financial Aid, 1965 (Box 33, Folder 9)
      - Government, General, 1964-1965 (Box 33, Folder 10)
      - Government, NASA, 1964-1965 (Box 33, Folder 11)
      - Government, National Science Foundation, 1964-1965 (Box 33, Folder 12)
      - J. Harvey - Consultant to the Chancellor, 1964 (Box 33, Folder 13)
      - Libraries, 1964 (Box 33, Folder 14)
      - Libraries, 1965 (Box 33, Folder 15)
      - New York State Department of Education, 1964 (Box 33, Folder 16)
      - Registrar, 1964-1965 (Box 33, Folder 17)
      - Research Services, Office of, 1961-1965 (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - Sub-Subseries C: Schools, Divisions, Institutes
      - Arts, School of, 1962-1963 (Box 34, Folder 1)
        bar code: 3 1142 042255086
      - Arts, School of, 1963-1964 (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - Arts, School of, 1964 (Box 34, Folder 3)
      - Arts, School of, 1964 (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - Arts, School of, 1965 (Box 34, Folder 5)
      - Arts, School of, 1965 (Box 34, Folder 6)
      - Commerce, School of, 1964-1965 (Box 34, Folder 7)
      - Courant Institute of Mathematics, 1964-1965 (Box 34, Folder 8)
      - Dentistry, College of, 1964-1965 (Box 34, Folder 9)
      - Education, School of, 1964 (Box 34, Folder 10)
      - Education, School of, 1965 (Box 34, Folder 11)
      - Education, School of - Committee to Select New Dean, 1964-1965 (Box 34, Folder 12)
      - Engineering, School of, 1964 (Box 34, Folder 13)
      - Engineering, School of, 1964-1965 (Box 35, Folder 1)
        bar code: 3 1142 042255094
      - Fine Arts, Institute of, 1964-1965 (Box 35, Folder 2)
      - General Education, Division of, 1963-1964 (Box 35, Folder 3)
      - General Education, Division of, 1964 (Box 35, Folder 4)
      - General Education, Division of, 1964-1965 (Box 35, Folder 5)
      - General Education, Division of - Committee to Select New Dean, 1964 (Box 35, Folder 6)
      - General Education, Division of - Committee to Select New Dean, 1964 (Box 35, Folder 7)
      - General Education, Division of - Committee to Select New Dean, 1965 (Box 35, Folder 8)
      - Graduate School of Arts and Science, 1964-1965 (Box 35, Folder 9)
      - Graduate School of Business Administration, 1964-1965 (Box 35, Folder 10)
      - Graduate School of Public Administration, 1964-1965 (Box 35, Folder 11)
      - Law, School of, 1964-1965 (Box 35, Folder 12)
      - Medicine, School of, 1964-1965 (Box 35, Folder 13)
      - Retailing, School of, 1964-1965 (Box 35, Folder 14)
      - Social Work, School of, 1964-1965 (Box 35, Folder 15)
      - University College of Arts and Science, 1964-1965 (Box 35, Folder 16)
      - University Valley - Sterling Forest, 1964-1965 (Box 35, Folder 17)